

# **ORNANDO LINOS**

•0812-6734-3437 • linosornando@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ornandolinos/

#### **SUMMARY**

An Industrial Engineering background with a strong foundation in continuous improvement well as experience working as a Data Analyst in the motorcycle automotive industry and as a Store Manager at Restaurant. My analytical and growth mindset have experience working in real-life situations make me confident in my ability to bring valuable insights and improvement to any project. I am excited to continue to develop my skills and grow as a professional in the field of any company.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Industrial Engineering**

September 2019 - September 2023

Parahyangan Catholic University

• Usulan Peningkatan Brand Awareness Restoran Ramen Noods Lab

GPA 3.42/4.00

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Store Manager

September 2023 - August 2024

#### PT. Noods Lab Indonesia (Ramen Restaurant)

- Oversee and manage all aspects of the restaurant's operations, including staffing, scheduling, and training.
- Manage inventory levels and order supplies to meet demand while minimizing waste and controlling costs.
- Implement and enforce company policies and procedures, including food safety standards and operational protocols.
- Ensure excellent customer service by maintaining high standards of hospitality and resolving any customer complaints or issues promptly.
- Develop and maintain positive relationships with suppliers, vendors, and other business partners.

# **Data Analyst Intern**

**August 2022 - January 2023** 

#### PT. Daya Adicipta Motora (Honda Jawa Barat)

- Honda Customer Care Center Division Customer Knowledge and Management Department
- Engage in research and information gathering to product insightful visualization
- Utilizing user-friendly visualization tools like Microsoft PowerBI to create an interactive dashboard
- Create a daily report regarding the data leads and assign data leads to dealers for service follow-up
- Utilizing programming languages like Python to perform data mining by RFM analysis approach on the customer database to create a customer segmentation for customer retention

#### **ORGANIZATIONS**

#### **Deputy Coordinator Public Relations of I TRAINEE 2021**

April 2021 - September 2021

- Make and send mail merge invitation to participants
- Looking for and contacting companies to become speaker for the event
- Become a Liason Officer for Happy Fresh Speaker

# Staff in Public Relations of OPEN HOUSE 2021

Feb 2021 - April 2021

- Become a Liason Officer for HMPSTI Division presentation
- Make Linktree for the event

LANGUAGE

English - TOEFL 552 - EF SET C2 (73/100) Chinese Mandarin Bahasa Indonesia

**SKILLS** 

Python Excel SQL PowerBl Tableau Lean Six Sigma Tools

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

**Python for Data Science dan Machine Learning** 

January 2022

Udemy

**Complete SQL Bootcamp: Go from Zero to Hero** 

Mar 2023

Udemy

**Lean Six Sigma Green Belt** 

August 2022

Perhimpunan Manajemen Mutu Indonesia (Indonesia Quality Management Association)